Ignoring your friends!
I can't believe that's the kind of captain
you turned out to be!
I thought you were better than that!
You're not being fair, Usopp.
Luffy felt...
You stay out of this!
It was my call, I stand by it!
There's nothing you can do!
We're getting a new ship, whether you like it or not!
This is the end of the road for the Mary!
I know you're always trying to think about the future,
but not everyone on this crew is like that!
I see the Mary as one of our friends, got it?
And I won't abandon her when she's hurt!
Don't be stupid!
Even if she is a friend, that doesn't mean she's a person!
She is to me, and she still has the strength to live!
But you wouldn't appreciate that,
cause all you care about is getting a new ship to play with!
Oh wait, that's enough!
Both of you just calm down and we can settle the same!
Dude, listen to yourself!
Luffy, don't act like you're the only one
who's torn up about this!
We all feel the same way!
If that was true, then you wouldn't be looking for a new ship!
All right, fine!
If you don't like the way your captain does things,
then why don't you go ahead and get on...
Sanji!
This is going way too far!
What the hell is wrong with you?
If you don't watch it, you're gonna say something you can't take back!
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I don't know what I was thinking.
You don't have to apologize, cause that's how you really feel, isn't it?
That's not true!
Well, just get rid of your dead weight and move on before they can slow you down!
If you're gonna throw away the Mary, might as well throw me away too!
You don't want weak people on your crew, do you?
Luffy, I still believe that you'll be King of the Pirates one day.
But as for me, I'm just lucky I was able to make it this far.
Hey, Usopp, where are you going?
Wherever I go, it's my business.
It has nothing to do with you anymore.
I'm leaving the crew.
This is goodbye.
Usopp!
Get back here!
It shouldn't be like this!
Come on!
We can talk!
Luffy, I'm sorry I can't follow you anymore.
And I'm sorry I was a pain till the bitter end.
I know you're the captain of this ship, so the Mary belongs to you.
That's why I want you to fight me, Monkey D. Luffy!
I challenge you to a duel!
At 10 o'clock tonight, I'll be back.
So you better be ready for a fight, Captain!
I can't stop you from destroying your own ship, but if I win, I'm taking the Mary and leaving.
Either way, when we're done, the last bond between us will be broken.
Luffy vs. Usopp, collision of two men's prides!
I am Usopp, leader of the invincible nation of pirates who reign over this island!
You stand before a living legend, the most revered pirate who ever lived!
I am the great Captain Usopp!
That's pretty cool!
Shut your mouth or I'll shut it for you!
I'm a proud man and I won't stand for it!
This is your last warning, or you'll get to see why they call me Proud Usopp and not Pushover Usopp!
You guys take care!
I hope we meet again sometime!
How come?
Well, because I...
Are you anti-social or something?
I'm taking off for life on the high seas and I hope that we'll eventually meet again!
That's all!
What are you talking about?
Get on already!
Huh?
We're friends, right?
So get on!
What?
This is it?
I'm really a pirate captain now!
Don't be stupid, Usopp!
I'm the captain!
Dead!
So you didn't lose your nerve after all.
No matter how this battle ends, you can't regret it.
This is exactly what you asked for!
That's perfect!
Don't go easy on me!
I won't be the underdog this time!
In fact, I've already figured out a way to defeat you!
Shouldn't we stop this?
Usopp's injuries are pretty bad!
If you can't stand a watch, then go inside.
Make no mistake.
I'm not like any opponent you've faced before.
We've been friends a long time.
I know all your powers, all your strengths, and all of your weaknesses.
But there's something you don't know about me.
I have 8,000 men on my side!
If you don't surrender now, I'll order them to attack!
What?
Why didn't he tell me?
Seriously, just go inside.
If you're gonna fight, then at least take this seriously!
Ooooooh!
Sap-a-doo!
You have razor-sharp needles!
Stuck between all of your teeth!
It hurts just to imagine that!
I'm telling you, go inside.
You've got prickly cactus spines under your finger!
Gum-gum!
Pistol!
What happened?
Ustah, please don't die!
Special attack.
Ketchup star.
Pity for your enemy.
That's awfully arrogant, don't you think?
Flash dial!
Now special attack, Eggstar!
Again!
It stinks!
They're rotten!
Dammit, would you stop messing around already?
Ugh!
You think this is a joke, huh?
Cause I'm dead serious.
Oh yeah?
That's right!
This is the way I fight!
Careful, that gaping mouth of yours is gonna get burnt!
Special attack!
Tabasco star!
What?!
I wouldn't jump around too much if I were you, cause the whole battlefield is Keltrop Hell!
He's controlling the fight!
Listen Luffy!
You can pity me if you want, but I'm gonna beat you and take the Merry with me!
And I don't care what it takes!
Usopp.
Special attack, Pepperstar!
Like I said, I know you, so I know which attacks are gonna work the best!
Dammit!
This stuff stinks!
My mouth is burning!
And it hurts!
I'm not gonna give you an itch, you hear me?
Special attack, Shiniken shooting star!
No kitchen.
No.
No kitchen!
I'm using a breath dial!
You didn't notice the smell because of the rotten eggs.
Smoke?
I'm using a breath dial.
You didn't notice the smell because of the rotten eggs.
And now you're completely surrounded by gas.
Gas?
Don't tell me he...
Sorry.
Blame Star!
That one's gonna sting!
Bloopy! Enough!
I am Usopp, leader of the invincible nation of pirates who reign over this island!
You stand before a living legend, the most revered pirate who ever lived! I am the great Captain Usopp!
Captain Usopp!
That's pretty cool!
Shut your mouth or I'll shut it for you!
How come?
We're friends, right? So get on!
Hey, I see an island!
Awesome! I can't wait to check it out!
Alright, let's go!
Mary, full speed ahead!
Full speed ahead!
Yeah!
Cool!
Perfect!
Wow!
Exactly!
No!
Not that'd be a good time!
Yeah!
Thank you.
I can't take this anymore.
Luffy! Lusup!
I'm no fool. I realize it'll take more than that to beat you.
I know you, Luffy. You fight every battle with all your strength.
But I'm ready for any technique you've got.
Special attack.
Come, come.
Its battery!
Blasting cactus stars!
Triple exploding stars!
Gah!
Now Gawgawm!
It's Gawgawm!
It's time to put an end to this!
Gawgawm!
Bazooka!
Recognize this?
I bet that bazooka would've hurt.
Let's find out!
Impact!
He used an impact dial!
I won't lose to you!
I'm Usopp!
Leader of the Invincible Nation of Pirates who reign over this island!
Cheers to a new ship and a new crewmate!
Yeah!
So, how do you like this one?
Yeah, keep it!
That's the one!
Okay, it's all done!
Now the Going Mary has everything she could possibly need!
Kom Kom!
Usopp!
At least it's over now!
You idiot!
You knew it would end like this!
You knew you could never beat me!
It never beat me!
Why did this have to happen?
Do whatever you want with the Mary!
I won't let anything hold us back!
We're getting a new ship!
And sailing forward!
Hey! Let me sit up there!
Sorry Usopp, but this seat's reserved for the captain!
Oh! What are you making?
Let me see! Let me see!
Hold on! The Usopp factory is off limits till I finish this for Nami!
Guys, listen up!
I will go to Elbas someday!
To the village of warriors!
Yeah! Great!
It's the festival on the night before gold hunting!
So long Usopp!
It was fun!
Well, it lasted!
Chopper!
Leave him alone!
So long Usopp!
It was fun!
Well, it lasted!
Well, it's fun!
Champagneался who explodes.
That's horrible!
Mom Sopp!
They can't leave him alone humans who has been there yet!
No!
They can't, they're just sp icebergs
He isn't part of our crew anymore.
So what? I'm a doctor! It's my doctor dream!
It's bad enough that he lost the duel.
If you pity him at a time like this, you'll end up hurting him more than any of those injuries.
I'm sure you have good intentions, but all we can do now is give him dignity and defeat.
He knew that when he challenged Luffy to a duel, this is how it might end.
It's too much.
This is what it means to be captain.
You can't doubt yourself.
In times like these, if you lose your confidence,
then who can we have faith in?
Let's pack our things and go.
You know as well as me that after tonight, we can never return to this ship again.
That's it.
We'll be right back.
one piece severe shock hits the city of water iceberg targeted I'm gonna be king